How's it really going? The human world these days...
I'm trying to push myself, but...
You know, the magical girl...
Yes, I've heard about her.
Is it true?
Yes, from what I've heard.
Yes, sir.
Can we dance here?
Finally, we can start moving.
Do all the fans know about this?
Uh, no.
Oh, I see.
I don't want to show them.
I don't want to show it.
I want to see it.
Congratulations!
Here we go again this week!
I grew up in Stardust's sugar refueling room and I'm a kanko!
I'll get right to it.
I'd like to invite today's guest, this idol.
I'm Hikaru Noritsuki, from Inari Talk. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
She's very pretty. Thank you.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Akimoto-san, the orca who visited us before... said you're his idol friend.
Mr. Akimoto, the killer whale, mentioned Ritsuki's name as one of his idols.
Did you see it?
I saw it. - You did? Really? You're good friends?
I really like her and admire her.
I love her so much, I adore her.
I even went to Hanaka-chan's birthday party in Nagoya.
In private? Yes, in private.
I went to Nagoya by myself.
It's a lot of travel to go to Nagoya by yourself, isn't it?
Travel. From Tohoku.
Of course.
And after that, I went out to dinner with him.
You went on a trip by yourself and even went to dinner?
I made it?
I'm so happy.
I was happy? I was so happy.
Did you go home alone?
Yes, I did.
That's good.
Do you talk about each other's groups?
Yes, we do.
What's different? Not about work, but when you see each other?
We do talk about work.
Really?
What do you two talk about?
I'm sorry, I can't imagine.
I don't know. I was so nervous, I don't remember much.
I remember such a wonderful time.
I do.
I don't know. I was happy.
I remember that Onoka is very cute.
Riki-chan is cute, too.
Akimoto-san, too.
I'm sure that if we were face to face...
I don't remember what I said.
I don't remember at all.
Are you okay with that?
You didn't say anything crazy, did you? I just don't remember.
I didn't say anything.
I see.
That's how much fun I had.
It was fun.
I see.
Well...
Ritsuki-san...
You've appeared on this show before, too.
In the style event of announcer Yoshida with Japan.
Are you a regular member of the Idol Singing Club?
Yes, I am.
Then sing a song.
What was the song again?
Five, seven.
A single song.Single song.
Five, seven, five, seven, seven.
Five-seven-five-seven-seven.
Oh, I see.
You can do it.
Yes, I can.
I see.
Did you just take over for me?
I can do it.
Thank you very much.
In five, seven, five, seven, seven.
Eh...
Yoshida-san, lately...
Excuse me, sir. A little bit of this...
You gave us a little directive, didn't you?
I'm sorry, sir.
I was told to keep you talking.
That's what he told me too.
I'm sorry I don't know any songs.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, I can't get involved in a love triangle.
When Mr. Northeast comes to see me...
Yes.
I love it.
It's nice.
Yes, it's good.
What? What?
What? You want to take a pass with me?
Sure.
Here we go.
Here you go. Cheese.
Thank you. - Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Kettle and Idols
I'm a magical girl.
Yes, I heard that soooooooooooooooooooooo
Sent to you courtesy of Bachchan.
Thank you everyone, rabbit.